module.exports = [
  {
<<<<<<< HEAD
    question: 'What is Weird Al Yankovic\'s first name?', 
    a: 'Weird',
    b: 'Jebediah',
    c: 'Matthew',
    d: 'Alfred',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What condition does "Denorex" treat?', 
    a: 'Nail Fungus',
    b: 'Dandruff',
    c: 'Excessive Flatulence',
    d: 'Erectile Dysfunction',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'A female fox is called a ___', 
    a: 'Fienna',
    b: 'Vixen',
    c: 'Fennec',
    d: 'Reynard',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What shoe company donates a pair of shoes to an impoverished child with every purchase?', 
    a: 'Naot',
    b: 'Keds',
    c: 'TOMS',
    d: 'Vans',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was famous for the phrase "The unexamined life is not worth living"?', 
    a: 'Plato',
    b: 'Socrates',
    c: 'William Shakespeare',
    d: 'John Donne',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT a La Croix flavor?', 
    a: 'Kiwi Sandia',
    b: 'Mure Pepino',
    c: 'Naranja Platano',
    d: 'Pomme Baya',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What album did Enimen\'s song "The Real Slim Shady" appear on?', 
    a: 'The Slim Shady LP ',
    b: 'The Marshall Mathers LP',
    c: 'The Eminem Show',
    d: 'Encore',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is the official mascot for Pringles chips?', 
    a: 'Mr. Pringle',
    b: 'Julius Pringles',
    c: 'Chester',
    d: 'Pritchard Pringle',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following was named "Sexiest Man Alive" by People Magazine?', 
    a: 'Christian Bale',
    b: 'Mel Gibson',
    c: 'Robert Downey Jr.',
    d: 'Will Smith',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was the name of Aladdin\'s pet monkey?', 
    a: 'Bubu',
    b: 'Iago',
    c: 'Abu',
    d: 'Abdul',
    answer: 'c'
  }
];